Guide to the Louis H. Roddis Papers, 1823-1990 RL.01102
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Gould, 1973-1986 and undated
  - Systems Protection Division Visit, 1984 May 24; Systems and Simulation Division Visit, 1984 May 30; and Defense Electronics Division Visit, 1984 June 5 (Box 65)
  - GGS, 1984 May 2 (Box 65)
  - Defense Systems Business Section 1986 Operating Plan, 1985 Nov. 4, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Gould, Inc. Monthly Operating Report, 1985 Sept.-Oct. (Box 65)
  - Global Settlement, 1985 Sept. 30 (Box 65)
  - Defense Systems Marketing Data Report, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence, 1985 Sept. 27 (Box 65)
  - Gould, Inc. Monthly Operating Report, 1985 Aug. (Box 65)
  - Gould. Inc. Task Outline, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence, 1985 Aug. 28 (Box 65)
  - Spare Parts Refund Policy, 1985 Aug. 26 (Box 65)
  - Gould, Inc. Monthly Operating Report, 1985 June-July (Box 65)
  - Gould News Release, 1985 Aug. 2 (Box 65)
  - Gould, Inc. Monthly Operating Reports, 1985 Aug.-Dec. (Box 65)
  - Correspondence, 1985 Sept. (Box 65)
  - NavCom, 1985 July 2 (Box 65)
  - Gould ATD, 1985 June 14 (Box 65)
  - Defense Systems Business Section 1986-1990 Strategic Plan, 1985 May 29 (Box 65)
  - Defense Systems Business Section Operating Board Meeting, 1985 May 29 (Box 65)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1985 Dec. 8-9 (Box 65)
  - Nominating Commitee Meeting, 1985 Dec. 7 (Box 65)
  - Gould Government Systems Operating Board Meeting, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 65)
  - Security Awareness Packet, 1985 Apr. 1 (Box 65)
  - Gould Research Center Strategic Plan and Memoranda, 1985 July 1 (Box 65)
  - Gould Research Laboratory, 1984 Jan. 23 (Box 65)
  - Gould Research Advisory Council and Board, 1985 Aug. 26-27 (Box 65)
  - Gould Research Center Operating Plan, 1986 (Box 65)
  - Potential Acquisition of SPD, 1986 Feb. 10 (Box 65)
  - Thank You Note for Rickover Foundation Donation, 1986 Mar. 31 (Box 65)
  - Gould, Inc. Monthly Operating Report, 1986 Apr. 14 (Box 65)
  - News Release on Adcap Torpedo Contract, 1986 Apr. 15 (Box 65)
  - Minutes of Bi-Annual Business Development/Engineering Meeting, 1985 Nov. 22 (Box 65)
  - Army Material Command (AMC) Pamphlet 70-7, 1984 (Box 65)
  - Gould, Inc. Monthly Operating Report, 1985 Dec. (Box 66)
  - Memorandum on Business Development/Engineering Meeting, 1985 Oct. 18, Nov. 22 (Box 66)
  - Gould, Inc. Standard Practice Procedure (SPP), 1985 Nov. 7 (Box 66)
  - News Release, 1985 Oct. 31 (Box 66)
  - Correspondence, 1985 Nov. 4 (Box 66)
  - Wilorco Acquisition Business Plan, 1985 Oct. 31 (Box 66)
- Long Island Lighting Company (LILCO), 1965-1989 and undated (bulk 1980s)
  Includes legal papers in the form of exhibits, cross-examinations, rebuttals, and testimonies, LILCO Board meeting minutes and annual reports, articles, clippings, reports, and an executive summary. LILCO is a utility company that faced bankruptcy in the mid 1980s due to its nuclear venture, the 4.1 billion dollar Shoreham facility. The State of New York Public Service Commission ordered an investigation, which lasted over fifteen years, of the Shoreham Nuclear Power Project. Issues discussed deal with the financial troubles of the Shoreham facility particularly and the company as a whole. Testimonies are from LILCO executives, qualitity assurances personnel, project management, engineering management, and construction management. Proceedings concerned LILCO's management decisions including associated construction methods, cost increases, and project controls. Some information on the Detroit Consolidated Edison Company's dealings with the State of Michigan's Public Service Commission in order to ammend rates and Trans-Alaska Pipeline System issues are found in this series.
  - Direct Testimony of Dr. Matthew C. Cordado, 1981 Nov. 2, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Supplemental Testimony of Dr. Matthew C. Cordado, 1982 Mar. 12 (Box 66)
  - Direct Testimony of Joseph Kelly and Robert Bernard, 1983 Nov. 4 (Box 66)
  - Direct Testimony of Wilfred O. Uhl, 1983 Nov. 4 (Box 66)
  - Rebuttal Testimony, 1984 May 15 (Box 66)
  - Exhibits to Rebuttal Testimony, 1984 May 15, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Cross Examination of Osborne, 1984 June 7 (Box 66)
  - Detroit Edison Company, 1984 July 25 (Box 67)
  - Cross Examination of Uhl Direct, 1984 May 15-16 (Box 67)
  - Reports Regarding Shoreham Progress, 1974-1984 (Box 67)
  - Report to LILCO on the Shoreham Nuclear Power Station, 1984 Feb. 3 (Box 67)
  - Long Island Lighting Company-Stone and Webster Contracts, 1967-1984 (Box 67)
  - Illionois Power--Love Testing, 1979-1984 (Box 67)
  - Theodore Barry and Associates, 1979 Mar. (Box 67)
  - Kaiser Engineers Power Corporation, 1979 Aug. (Box 67)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of Roger S. Byrd, 1984 May 15 (Box 67)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of Howard R. Canter, 1984 May 15 (Box 67)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of Thomas J. Burke, 1984 May 15 (Box 67)
  - Exhibits to Rebuttal Testimony of Thomas J. Burke, 1984 May 15 (Box 67)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of Russell C Youngdahl, 1984 May 15 (Box 67)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of Adam M. Madsen, 1984 May 15 (Box 67)
  - Exhibits to Rebuttal Testimony of Adam M. Madsen, 1984 May 15 (Box 68)
  - Exhibits to Rebuttal of Feeley, Golden, Gonzaga, Heuchling, Osborne, and Smith, 1984 May 15, 3 folders (Box 68)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of J. Ronald Fox, 1984 May 15 (Box 68)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of J. Ronald Fox, 1984 May 15 (Box 68)
  - Exhibits to the Rebuttal Testiminy of J. Ronald Fox, 1984 May 15 (Box 68)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of Joseph P. Navarro, 1984 May 15 (Box 68)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of John T. Stieffel, 1984 May 15 (Box 68)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of George A. Avery, 1984 May 15 (Box 68)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of Louis. H. Roddis, Jr. 1984 May 15 (Box 69)
  - Articles, 1988 Dec. 6-7 (Box 69)
  - Correspondence, 1985 Oct. 7 (Box 69)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1965 Jan. 1-1971 Feb. 23, 10 folders (Box 69)
  - Roddis's Long Island Lighting Company Appointment Book, 1984 (Box 69)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of Louis H. Roddis, Jr., 1984 May 3 (Box 69)
  - Questions on Testing, 1967 and 1984 (Box 69)
  - Long Island Lighting Company Annual Reports, 1966-1984 (Box 69)
  - Cadwalader, Wickersham and Taft (CWT)--General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 69)
  - Nuclear Plant Data 1984 (Box 69)
  - Summary, undated (Box 69)
  - LILCO/Shoreham Facility-Press Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 69)
  - LILCO--Prudency, 1984 (Box 69)
  - LILCO-Public Service Commission Order 27563, 1979 May 21 (Box 69)
  - Interviews with Long Island Lighting Company Board, 1982-1984 (Box 69)
  - Long Island Lighting Company-Events, 1984 Jan. 27 (Box 69)
  - Review of Board Books and Minutes, 1984 Apr. (Box 69)
  - CWT Testimony Notes, 1984 Feb. (Box 69)
  - Material for Lou Roddis, 1984 Apr. 17 (Box 70)
  - Investigation Articles and Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 70)
  - New York Department of Public Service Summany, ca. 1984 (Box 70)
  - Quality Programs Testimony Exhibits, 1984 Feb. (Box 70)
  - Quality Programs Testimony, 1984 Feb. (Box 70)
  - Executive Summary, 1984 Feb. 10 (Box 70)
  - Project Management and Owner Oversight Testimony, 1984 Feb. (Box 70)
  - Construction Management Testimony, 1984 Feb (Box 70)
  - Construction Management Testimony Exhibits, 1984 Feb., 4 folders (Box 70)
  - Engineering Management Testimony, 1984 Feb. (Box 70)
  - Direct Testimony of Gregory A. Palast, 1984 Feb. 10 (Box 70)
  - Direct Testimony of Rudolph Bertschi, 1984 Feb. 3 (Box 70)
  - Direct Testimony of David Bridenbaugh, Lynn M. Danielson, Richard B. Hubbard, and Gregory C. Minor, 1984 Feb. 10 (Box 70)
  - Exhibits to the Testimony of Bridenbaugh, Danielson, Hubbard, and Minor, 1984 Feb. 10 (Box 70)
  - Direct Testimony of Robert J. Allio, Paul C. Rizzo, and John M. Musacchio, 1984 Feb. 3 (Box 71)
  - Documentary Exhibits to the Testimony of Allio, Rizzo, and Musacchio, 1984 Feb. 3, 2 folders (Box 71)
  - Quantification Testimony and Exhibits, 1984 Feb. (Box 71)
  - Quality Programs Testimony Vol. 2, 1984 Feb. (Box 71)
  - Engineering Management Testimony Exhibits Vol. 1-5, 1984 Feb., 5 folders (Box 71)
  - Project Management and Owner Oversight Exhibits Vol. 1-6, 1984 Feb., 6 folders (Box 71)
  - Diesel Generator Testimony, 1984 Feb. (Box 72)
  - Diesel Generator Testimony Exhibits Vol. 1-3, 1984 Feb., 3 folders (Box 72)
  - Regulatory Relations Testimony, 1984 Feb. (Box 72)
  - Regulatory Relations Testimony Exhibits Vol. 1-3, 1984 Feb., 3 folders (Box 72)
  - Direct Testimony of William J. Museler, 1983 Nov. 3 (Box 72)
  - Direct Testimony of William J. Museler and Edward J. Youngling, 1983 Nov. 4 (Box 72)
  - Direct Testimony of William S. Pollock and Joseph P. Novarro, 1983 Nov. 4 (Box 72)
  - Direct Testimony of William J. Museler, 1983 Nov. 4 (Box 73)
  - Direct Testimony of William J. Museler and William R. Sheridan, 1983 Nov. 3 (Box 73)
  - Direct Testimony of Brian R. McCaffrey, 1983 Nov. 4 (Box 73)
  - Direct Testimony of J. Ronald For in Trans-Alaska Pipeline System Case, undated, 2 folders (Box 73)
  - Booz-Allen Hamilton Report on Major Project Management, 1978 Aug. 25, 2 folders (Box 73)
  - Long Island Lighting Company's Proposed Findings of Fact in the Area of Product Management, 1984 Dec. 21 (Box 73)
  - Recommended Decision by Administrative Law Judges William C. Levy and Thomas R. Matias, 1985 Mar. 13 (Box 73)
  - The Initial Brief of the Long Island Lighting Company to the Administrative Law Judge, 1984 Dec. 21, 2 folders (Box 73)
  - Long Island Lighting Company Takeover: A Better Deal?, 1986 June 25 (Box 73)
  - Will a Government Takeover of Long Island Lighting Company Save Money for Consumers?, 1986 Mar. 31 (Box 73)
  - Report on Public Understanding of Nuclear Energy, 1985 July (Box 73)
  - Long Island Lighting Company Securities Litigation, 1985 Feb. 4 (Box 73)
  - First Ammended and Consolidated Class Action Complaint in Long Island Lighting Company Securities Litigation, 1988 Feb. 4 (Box 74)
  - The Energy Daily, 1989 Apr. 25 (Box 74)
  - Rebuttal Testimony of Louis H. Roddis, Jr., 1984 May 15 (Box 74)
- Washington Public Power Supply Systems (WPPSS) 1979-1984 and undated
  Contains correspondence, memoranda, reports, notes, meeting packets, clippings, and articles. The WPPSS is a Pacific Northwest utilities company. The primary issue discussed is the company's financial troubles, especially of the company's nuclear reactor the Washington Nuclear Plant-2. The series represents the methodical audit of the entire design and construction processes conducted by in-house teams. Their purpose was to provide WPPSS and others with the best assurance attainable that the design fulfills all that is required of it and that what was designed has been faithfully preserved in construction. Roddis worked on the independent review team which served to evaluate and criticize the procedures, scope, and conduct of the in-house effort, point out inadequacies, recommend improvements and express confidence in results.
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 74)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Interoffice Memorandum, 1981 June 29 (Box 74)
  - Report of the Engineering Review Team to the Washington Public Power Supply System, 1981 Feb. 12 (Box 74)
  - Appendix B to Report of the Engineering Review Team, 1981 Feb. 12 (Box 74)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System--Staffing, 1980-1981 (Box 74)
  - Commonwealth Edison- Washingon Public Power Supply System Organization, 1981 Jan. (Box 74)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System- Duke Power Company Staff Data, 1980 Dec. (Box 74)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System- General Public Utilities Organization, 1980 (Box 74)
  - Articles, 1980 Dec.-1981 Jan. (Box 74)
  - Progress Report No. 99, 1980 Nov. 30 (Box 74)
  - Progress Report No. 111, 1981 Jan. 16 (Box 74)
  - The Washington State Senate Energy and Utilities Committee-- Washington Public Power Supply System Inquiry, 1980 Oct. 10 (Box 74)
  - EBASCO, 1981, June 28-29 (Box 74)
  - Correspondence, 1981 Jan. 20 (Box 74)
  - Report of the Engineering Review Team to the Washington Public Power Supply System, 1981 Feb. 12 (Box 74)
  - EBASCO Management Centralization Plan for Washington Public Power Supply System, 1980 July (Box 74)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Draft Report, 1980 Dec. 21 (Box 74)
  - EBASCO Room Rate Sheet, undated (Box 74)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Interoffice Memorandum, 1980 Dec. 23 (Box 74)
  - Combustion Engineering, Inc. System 80 Nuclear Steam Supply System, undated (Box 74)
  - Notes of 1980-1981 SWAT Team Meetings, 1981 Jan. 9 (Box 74)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System 3-5, 1981 Jan. 5-9 (Box 74)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System 1 and 4, 1980 Dec. 12 (Box 74)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Nuclear Projects Nos. 1 and 4 Follow-Up Input to SWAT Team Visit, undated (Box 74)
  - Progress Report No. 98, 1980 Oct. 31 (Box 74)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System/UE&C Management Meeting, 1980 Dec. 17-18, 2 folders (Box 75)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Nos. 1 and 4, 1980 Dec. 1-5 (Box 75)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Nos. 3-5, 1980 Dec. 1 (Box 75)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System No. 2, 1980 Nov. (Box 75)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System No. 2--General Electric, 1980 Dec. 5 (Box 75)
  - Burns and Roe, 1980 Nov. 19 (Box 75)
  - Progress Report No. 96, 1980 Aug. 31 (Box 75)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Meeting, 1980 Nov. 5 (Box 75)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Letter, 1980 Oct. 21 (Box 75)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Letter, 1980 Oct. 20 (Box 75)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Annual Report, 1980 (Box 75)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Generating Facilities Revenue Bonds Series 1980 1980 Sept. 23 (Box 75)
  - Final Report--Assessment of 1980 Project Construction Budgets, 1979 Nov. 16 (Box 75)
  - Plant Verification Program Plan, 1982 Apr. 9 (Box 75)
  - Memorandum, 1982 Feb. 16 (Box 75)
  - Plant Verification Program Meeting Agenda, 1982 Apr. 26 (Box 75)
  - Information on Washington Public Power Supply System, 1982 Apr. (Box 75)
  - Performance Objectives and Criteria for Project Evaluations, 1982 Apr. 12 (Box 75)
  - Correspondence, 1982 Mar. 11 (Box 75)
  - Article, 1982 Apr. 20 (Box 75)
  - Memorandum, 1982 Apr. 17 (Box 75)
  - Resumes for Andre I. Cygleman, Geoffrey L. Gelhaus, Silvio A. Giusti, and Roger T. Johnson, undated (Box 75)
  - TAA Internal Topical Report T 26-00, 1982 Apr. 13 (Box 75)
  - Operating Envelope Verification, undated (Box 75)
  - WNP-2 Plant Verification Plan, 1982 Apr. 9 (Box 75)
  - Correspondence, 1982 Apr. 20 (Box 76)
  - Plant Verification Program Meeting Agenda, 1982 Apr. 26 (Box 76)
  - Engineering Resources, undated (Box 76)
  - Agenda for Visit by Technical Audit Associates, 1982 Apr. 24 (Box 76)
  - Requirements and Design Verification, undated (Box 76)
  - WNP-2 Completion Plan, undated (Box 76)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System, 1982 May 24-25 (Box 76)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System-TAA, 1982 June 25 (Box 76)
  - Louis H. Roddis, Jr. Notes for Phase 1A Review Panel Meeting, 1982 June 25 (Box 76)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Report, 1982 May 24-25 (Box 76)
  - WNP-2 Project Reverification Report, 1982 Apr., 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous TAA 1126, 1982 Dec.-1983 Jan. (Box 76)
  - TAA-NRC Meeting, 1982 Nov. 10 (Box 76)
  - WNP-2 Materials, 1982 Dec. 14 (Box 76)
  - Residual Heat Removal System, 1982 Nov. 5 (Box 76)
  - Reactor Feedwater System, 1982 Dec. 9 (Box 76)
  - Awards Panel Response Form, 1982 Dec. 2 (Box 76)
  - High Pressure Core Spray System, 1982 Dec. 9 (Box 76)
  - TAA Trip Notes, 1982 Nov. 19-22 (Box 76)
  - WNP-2 PV Report Rev. 1, 1982 Nov. 1 (Box 76)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Offerings, 1982 May 1 (Box 76)
  - WNP-2 Turbine, 1982-1983 (Box 76)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Chemistry, 1982 (Box 76)
  - WNP-2 Procedures, 1982 Sept. 1 (Box 76)
  - NRC Practical Construction, 1982 (Box 76)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 76)
  - In-Process Construction Related Documentation, 1982 Sept (Box 77)
  - WNP-2 Program Director's Monthly Progress Report, 1982 Aug. (Box 77)
  - Systems Completion Reverification Report for Contract 210A, 1982 Oct. 12 (Box 77)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Materials, 1982 Sept. 15 (Box 77)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Meeting, 1982 Oct. 13-15 (Box 77)
  - Phase 2, 1982 Sept. 10 (Box 77)
  - WNP-2 Audits First, 1982 (Box 77)
  - WNP-2 Progress Reports 6-10, 1981-1982 (Box 77)
  - WNP-2 Progress Reports 3, 4, and 5, 1981 (Box 77)
  - WNP-2 Progress Report 1, 1980 Oct. 16 (Box 77)
  - WNP-2 Progress Report 2, 1980 Dec. 20 (Box 77)
  - WNP-2 Visit--Notes, 1983 Apr. 27-29 (Box 77)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 77)
  - Memoranda, 1983 (Box 77)
  - Potential Findings Report Transmittal, 1983 Apr. 12 (Box 77)
  - Design Reverification Plans, 1983 Apr. 18 (Box 77)
  - Hanford No. 2 Engineering Criteria Document, undated (Box 77)
  - NRC Inspections, 1983 Mar. (Box 77)
  - Other Reports, 1983 Mar.-Apr. (Box 77)
  - WNP-2 Audit Reports, 1983 (Box 77)
  - Response to TAA Audit Report Dated 1983, Jan. 10; 1983 Mar. 8 (Box 77)
  - Correspondence, 1983 Mar. 14 (Box 77)
  - Notes on NSSS Corrosion, 1983 Mar. 9 (Box 77)
  - Correspondence, 1983 Feb. 17 (Box 77)
  - In-Process Construction Related Documentation, 1983 Jan. (Box 77)
  - TAA Findings, 1983 Feb. 10 (Box 77)
  - Quality Verification Program (Attachment M), undated (Box 77)
  - Report of Audit No. 2 of the Washington Public Power Supply (Box 77)
  - System Plant Reverification Program for WNP-2, 1983 Feb. 15 (Box 77)
  - Nuclear Project No. 2 WNP-2 Test Program, 1983 Feb. 9 (Box 77)
  - Municipal Bond Research on Washington Public Power Supply System, 1983 Jan. 31 (Box 77)
  - Corrected Transmittal Forms for Potential Findings Reports, undated (Box 77)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System-Nuclear Regulatory Commission Letters Regarding TAA, 1982 Dec. (Box 77)
  - Growth and Nozzle Load Letters, 1983 Feb. 17 (Box 77)
  - Trip Questions and Notes, 1983 Jan. 26 (Box 77)
  - Interactive Design Review, 1983 Jan. 18 (Box 77)
  - Miller Report No. 3 for TAA, 1983 Jan. 26 (Box 77)
  - Trip Items to Ask, 1983 Jan. 26 (Box 78)
  - TAA Trip Information, 1983 Jan. 26 (Box 78)
  - TAA Draft Audit Report, 1982 Dec. 15 (Box 78)
  - TAA Meeting in New York, 1983 Jan. 5 (Box 78)
  - Package Nuclear Regulatory Commission Inspection, 1983 Jan. 21 (Box 78)
  - Package B Audit Reports, 1983 Jan. 21 (Box 78)
  - Manual on Design Verification, 1982 Dec. 9 (Box 78)
  - Requirements Reverification Report, 1983 Jan. 17, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - WNP-2 Program Director's Monthly Progress Report, 1982 Oct. (Box 78)
  - WNP-2 Program Director's Monthly Progress Report, 1982 Sept.. (Box 78)
  - WNP-2 Program Director's Monthly Progress Report, 1983 Mar. (Box 78)
  - WNP-2 Program Director's Monthly Progress Report, 1983 Feb. (Box 78)
  - WNP-2 Program Director's Monthly Progress Report, 1983 Jan. (Box 78)
  - WNP-2 Program Director's Monthly Progress Report, 1982 Nov. (Box 78)
  - WNP-2 Program Director's Monthly Progress Report, 1982 Dec. (Box 78)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System Residual Heat Removal, 1983 July (Box 78)
  - Reactor Feedwater Final, undated (Box 78)
  - HPCS, 1983 Aug. 3 (Box 78)
  - Design Reverification Final, undated (Box 78)
  - QVP Final Draft, 1983 Aug. 15 (Box 78)
  - Audit Report No. 4 Final, 1983 Aug. 29 (Box 78)
  - Corrective Action Plans for Closure of Design Reverification Findings, 1983 July 25 (Box 78)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 78)
  - TAA WNP-2 Final Draft, 1983 Aug. 16 (Box 78)
  - Miller HCPS, 1983 July 12 (Box 78)
  - WNP-2 Materials, 1983 July 20-22 (Box 78)
  - Agendas and Notes, 1983 July 20-22 (Box 78)
  - Transmittal, 1983 June 22 (Box 78)
  - Transmittal, 1983 July 14 (Box 78)
  - Transmittal, 1983 June 21 (Box 78)
  - Transmittal, 1983 July 11 (Box 78)
  - Agenda Handouts for Meeting, 1983 July 20 (Box 79)
  - Transmittal, 1983 July 7 (Box 79)
  - Transmittal, 1983 July 13 (Box 79)
  - CYGNA- Detroit Edison, 1983 Apr. 29 (Box 79)
  - CYGNA-Grand Gulf, 1982 July 30 (Box 79)
  - Torrey Pines--Palo Verde, 1982 Oct. (Box 79)
  - TPTech-Zimmer, 1983 Aug. (Box 79)
  - Planned Studies of Quality Assurance Programs for Construction of Nuclear Power Plants, 1983 May 6 (Box 79)
  - TAA Audit Reports on WNP-2, 1983 May 11 (Box 79)
  - TAA Audit Report No. 2 on WNP-2, 1983 Feb. 15 (Box 79)
  - TAA Audit Report No. 1 on WNP-2, 1983 Jan. 12 (Box 79)
  - WNP-2 Package, 1983 May 26 (Box 79)
  - WNP-2 Package, 1983 May 13 (Box 79)
  - WNP-2 Package, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Technical Audit Associates Comments, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Nozzle Loads and Fire Hazard Evaluation for the RHR System, 1983 (Box 79)
  - WNP-2 Potentially Reportable Deficiency, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Potential Finding Reports for Reactor Feedwater (RFW) Systems, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Finding Review Committee Meeting, 1983, March (Box 79)
  - Potential Finding Reports and Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 79)
  - WNP-2 Design Reverification Status Meeting, 1983, April 20 (Box 79)
  - Potential Finding Reports for RHR System, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Potential Finding Reports for HPCS, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Status of Bonneville Power Administration's Efforts to Improve Its Oversight of Three Nuclear Power Projects, report by the Comptroller General of the United States, 1984, Aug. 3 (Box 79)
  - Technical Audit Associates Correspondence, 1983, Oct. (Box 79)
  - Design Reverification Draft, 1983, Sept. (Box 79)
  - C. Q. Miller's Final Disposition Analysis, 1983, Sept. (Box 79)
  - Technical Audit Associates Final Quality Verification Program (QVP) Report, 1983, Sept. (Box 79)
  - Technical Audit Associates New York Meeting, 1983, August 25-26 (Box 79)
  - Technical Audit Associates New York, 1983, Sept. 12 (Box 79)
  - Design Reverification, Draft Vol. 2, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Technical Audit Associates QVP DraftVol. 1, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Fourth WPPSS Audit Report, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Clippings, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Technical Audit Associates Project 1126 Bibliography, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Potential Findings Reports, 1983, July (Box 80)
  - Burns and Roe Response Package, 1983 (Box 80)
  - C. Q. Miller's First Disposition Analysis, 1983, Sept. (Box 80)
  - GE Hanford Systems Instalation Review, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Herman E. Sheets Correspondence, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Evaluation of Burns and Roe Design Closure, 1983 (Box 80)
  - WPN-2 Project Weekly Reports, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Johnson Controls, Inc. Audit Reports, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Technical Audit Associates Final First Draft, 1983, Aug. 3 (Box 80)
  - QVP Overview Draft, 1983 Aug. (Box 80)
  - Construction Appraisal Team and Response, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Requirements Reverification Report, 1983, Aug. 19 (Box 80)
  - Findings Review Committee Transmittals, 1983, 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Requests for Action Letters, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Corrective Action Letters, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Technical Audit Associates New York, 1983, Oct. 10 (Box 80)
  - Technical Audit Associates New York, 1983, Sept. 27-28 (Box 80)
  - Technical Audit Associates Design Reverification Requirements Draft, 1983, Sept. 21 (Box 80)
  - Technical Audit Associates Draft of Summary and Conclusions, 1983, Oct. 9 (Box 80)
  - T echnical Audit Associates Appendix A to Draft of Summaries and Conclusion, 1983, Oct. 9 (Box 81)
  - WNP-2 Design Reverification Program, Volume I: Final Assessment Report, by WPPSS, 1983, Sept. (Box 81)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 81)
  - Memoranda, 1983, Sept. - Oct. (Box 81)
  - Burns and Roe, Inc.'s Evaluation of Potentially Reportable Conditions No. 278-280, 1983, Sept. (Box 81)
  - Correspondence with Burns and Roe, Inc., 1983, Aug. - Sept. (Box 81)
  - An Independent Evaluation of the Plant Verification Program at WNP-2, Volumes 1-3, by TAA, 1983 Sept., 3 folders (Box 81)